[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "We will facilitate growth and development in our ____ communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Try to ____ that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an instant solution.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Not everyone likes ____ webpages with lots of movement and sound.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Patients are ____ to forget information that is not written down.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The king could delay implementing a new law, but could not ____ it entirely.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "ESL students ____ better in classrooms where the teacher is aware of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As a result of the ____ amount of evidence for evolution accumulated over the last two centuries, we can safely conclude that evolution has occurred.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We ____ that circumstances beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The human mind cannot ____ the true nature of God, nor can the angels.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to ____ if the purpose of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Before economists implement ____ measures to reduce population growth, further studies should be performed.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There have been problems in the school ____ students of different nationalities.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein ____ the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not occupy much space.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ fits well with the fact that his mental health did not deteriorate.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most schools do a lot to ____ their students of the dangers of smoking.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh ____ that Black defendants have received at the hands of predominantly White jurors.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dr. Glick is an expert in ____ and public health nursing programs and issues.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The bottom of the Pacific Ocean is the most ____ region on Earth.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a valid excuse, you can ____ the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government must be prepared for an attack from people who ____ its decision.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Where can I ____ about the teaching job I saw in the newspaper?", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When morality comes up against profit, it is ____ profit that loses.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ structure of Iraqi military and civil society collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Simply exporting surplus graduates is not itself a policy problem if there is a ____ for those graduates.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want to live a long and healthy life, it is essential that you eat well and take get ____ of exercise.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Because of the increase in the price of oil the company was unable to ____ to its plans to employ new workers.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students need to ____ with the department offering the master's degree to ensure the correct credential courses are taken.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Scientists ____ that most children born today in First World countries will see their 75th birthday.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His beliefs were not firm enough to withstand the ____ of the people worked with.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Germany had to accept a ____ peace treaty after being defeated in the first world war.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to ____ an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This ____ is certain to improve over the next few years, given the quantity of research now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The supply of new doctors is getting low. Some ____ parts of the country will be without medical services if this situation does not change.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students must demonstrate ____ of a competent reading knowledge of a language other than modern English.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They did not provoke an ____. They responded to an ____ from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the ____ between teachers, parents and students, and improve the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many tourists to foreign countries buy a ____ book to help them speak a few words of the language.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "London is becoming more and more unpleasant. The government needs to drastically increase the ____ for dropping litter.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government must continue to make every ____ to prevent young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a ____ final exam.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A major ____ in his success was his willingness to work very hard.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most important thing to keep in mind as you begin working on your assignments is that a philosophy paper is not an ____ to be overcome but an opportunity to show what you have learned.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations ____ the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "People are more likely to ____ in times of war or economic poverty.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your report is good, but you need to ____ a paragraph on the causes of the accident.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The bank didn't think that her idea would ____ enough money so they refused to finance it.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There were many sane but ____ reasons why he gave up his well-paid job.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The patient was not at all happy with the standard of ____ she received while in hospital.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the impulse to improve his ____ poor grades.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "By the middle of May the ____ was critical and the rebellion seemed to get closer daily to the capital.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The final ____ presents the impact of traditional, sometimes outdated, teaching methods and their effect on the participants' learning.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We still don't know if this is really the correct ____ to explain the imbalance between matter and antimatter that we observe.", "Opt_1": "concern", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is an ____ piece of work. Well done!", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a unique search ____ has paid off.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Musical ability is a ____ that some people are born with, but no-one succeeds as a musician without an enormous amount of practice.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new ____ should help to reduce the number of problems resulting from adjustment to semester length.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She has been an important exponent, nationally and internationally, of the view that artists have a critical ____ to play in democratic societies.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the committee failed to ____ in sufficient detail the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has not been very successful in reducing teenage drinking, but it must ____ in its efforts.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please ____ the Timetable for class times and locations.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Just ____ someone wakes up after sleeping for thousand years. How might the world look different?", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are caught drinking and driving, this results in an ____ driving ban of at least 3 months.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ was too much for some, and owners were forced to sell their homes at a reduced price.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This we know: the earth does not ____ to man, man ____s to the earth.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You can buy each ____ on the school supplies list from the bookstore.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a ridiculous fear, but she was unable to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The late bus will ____ at 5:30 today, not at 5:15 as usual.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students must demonstrate evidence of a ____ reading knowledge of a language other than modern English.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Of course she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the initial ____ of learning English.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These findings suggest that something in the brain's pain-processing and pain-killing systems may ____ by race and ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While a ____ degree of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The report was designed to ____ computer and Internet use among people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Performance in the money markets has been consistent in recent months, but prices are expected to ____ in the near future.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teacher decided to ____ the activity when it became clear that the students didn't understand what to do.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences ____ improve performance over time.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She is trying to ____ a new way to open tin cans.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government thanked Greenpeace for the information but said that it wasn't ____ to its decision.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Results will be published in the ____ issue of the Canadian Journal of Fisheries and Aquatic Sciences.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The set of elective courses must constitute a well-defined ____ and must be approved by the student's advisor.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most comprehensive ____ of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The meeting will ____ at 8.30.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His new book is sure to ____ a lot of attention.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All this progress was a consequence of the ____ of technology and also of ____s in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Research strongly supports the notion that publishing houses lack ____ diversity in both high and middle-level staff members.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A ____ teaching methodology will not be successful in a class with many different nationalities and abilities.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a bold idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the ____ arts.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Roman Jewish population did not ____ during Sixtus' reign; indeed, there was always movement of Jews in and out of the region.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The VFWF reserves the right to ____ additional funds if the amount of the grant is insufficient to fully meet the needs.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new government has promised not to repeat the mistakes of the ____ one.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most children take a ____ of domestic duties such as washing the dishes.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was ____ that he did not do well in the vocabulary test. I know he had learned most of the words.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always ____ giving undivided attention to the organization.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best way to ensure that your machine has a unique name is to use your University ____ name for your computer name.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school has set up a ____ so that less wealthy students can attend.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The private ____ offers many opportunities for students with a history or liberal arts background.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "stage", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was not ____ to use the river as the source for your drinking water before you analyzed it.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The tale ends with Gilgamesh, at the end of his ____ standing before the gates of Uruk.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The instructor is expected to announce his or her grading ____ at the beginning of the course.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Not all the decisions of the ____ have been welcomed by the workers.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "People are right to be suspicious of any diet that promises ____ success.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She was quickly able to ____ the difficulty of speaking little English, and now she is easily the best student in the class.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your ____ is to learn the English words that will help you be successful in your school subjects.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and ____ not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A color model is an orderly system for creating a whole ____ of colors from a small set of primary colors.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the context of competitive sports, and ____ elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government will today publish its ____ report on crime statistics.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you are relocating to another U.S. school after your graduation, we will need to ____ your records to that school.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you can ____ your intelligence with hard work, you have a good chance of success.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The US government is considering if it should ____ its army from Iraq.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I gave you ____ instructions not to open the box. Why did you disobey me?", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The new government proposals also stipulate that all unemployed young people ____ a three-week training course once a year.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This report draws on lessons learned from ____ military deployments to consider strategies to protect the health of troops in future deployments.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can simultaneously make cannabis ____ and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ of an original idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Pick a global issue and collect a ____ of newspaper articles and/or news clips on it during the semester.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is extremely important to ____ the installation with all parties involved.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Sediment cores collected from the seafloor off Southern California ____ that plankton populations in the Northeastern Pacific have changed significantly.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please ____ me from the trip list. I will not be able to go.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't ____ with police orders to disperse from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse global ____ will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We will facilitate growth and development in our ____ communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "China has experienced ____ growth in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her family were persecuted by the Nazis, so it's no surprise that she shows ____ against the Germans.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "To ____ their high salary, top managers like to refer to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He has lost the desire to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, ____ devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The University of Maryland team is particularly focused on using their ____ to test drugs that may block cell-to-cell \"quorum-sensing\".", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Throughout the day, with a brief ____ for lunch, he stared at the history project which was due the next morning.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government must continue to make every effort to ____ young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the event of an ____ disaster a new virtual bulletin board will help the campus take roll.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is unable to ____ that Iran is planning to build nuclear weapons.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to fulfill the duties of the ____ teaching job.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Aside from the significant political ____ of the bill, it carries little weight and makes little difference.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A wife's going out to work is not deemed a violation of her marital obligations if her working is not ____ to her family's interests.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This issue is more ____ than we expected; we're going to need some outside help.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As the number of old people increases, so has the ____ that there is not enough money in the health system to take proper care of them.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The search results are likely to include lots of hits that are not particularly ____ to your topic.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When Penn State decided not to cancel classes, it seemed like a safe and ____ decision.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Emma was ____ of these various and strongly held opinions, through professional periodicals.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The airport police always ____ the need for everyone to be vigilant with their suitcases and other bags.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a serious ____ of workers in the profession of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most car companies are putting money into research into ____ forms of fuel. It will take a number of years, however, before anyone can develop a car that runs on water.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When he left home he planned to ____ from Christianity to Buddhism, but then he decided he didn't believe in any god.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We know it's not 100% correct, but it's the best ____ that we can produce at this time.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many young people fill in the ____ between school and university by travelling around the world for a few months.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Their acquaintance, therefore, it may be presumed, did not ____ till towards the end of this year 1754.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This brochure was created to help home owners and land managers recognize hazardous defects in trees and to ____ possible corrective actions.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want an ____ answer to almost any question you could ask, then Google will probably give it to you.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In order to ____ for the Olympic games 100-meter athletes need to have run under 10.2 seconds at least once this year.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to ____ the throne of Armenia, could not conceal his discontent.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We do not yet know the implication for the government of the rapid ____ in house prices.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Miller's path to UCSC was far from smooth, but her ____ and determination kept her moving toward her goal.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This document will ____ some of the problems that could exist because the computer is unable to install updates for Windows Vista.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I don't believe you made a ____ effort to improve. Your grades certainly have not got better.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "But you are forgetting one thing, gentlemen of the law, you are driving a horse to water but you cannot ____ him to drink.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Be sure to ____ and disinfect feeding equipment and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is a direct result of how the black hole deforms space and time, a four-dimensional ____ that Einstein called spacetime.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The agent's ____ for selling a house is usually a percentage of the sale price.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Should the government ____ more in solar energy or nuclear energy? It's a difficult choice.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Furthermore, the system can also ____ environmental conditions in the immediate surroundings including ambient light level, humidity, and temperature.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project ____ date.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There are very few people living today who were born ____ to the first world war.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The following information has been prepared to serve as a ____ to assist you in establishing criteria for a successful teaching practice.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not depart from the ____ requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most people ____ to drive to huge out-of-town stores than use their local shops which are often much more expensive.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In most modern car factories robots ____ the larger parts.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When you ____ the school, turn right and walk along the corridor. You will find the library on the left-hand side.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Why do some children seem willing to ____ while others do not?", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to ____ the amount of land available for pasture.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The board was unable to ____ a candidate in the first round because of disagreement over candidates' performance.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most ____ animal class is the insect. Insects come in thousands of shapes and colors.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Newspapers employ people to ____ the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We will not violate the personal ____ of co-workers and customers, and will respect their right to privacy.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teachers allege that the school ____ is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "manifest", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "show", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I did not understand what the artist was trying to express by these two pieces, nor did I see any ____ in the work.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "His behaviour has not been very ____ since he returned from vacation.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some doctors have suggested that their training should be less theoretical and of more ____ use.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was found, in a bad ____ of repair and covered with moss and rust.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A nursing or household robot must be ____ in order to reach a variety of working sites within the house.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If your parents want too take you out of school during term time, they must have a ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are many things that people can do in the battle ____ global warming. For instance, they can turn off lights when they leave the room.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My science teacher returned my homework and told me to do it again. She said I had to use the ____ format for lab reports.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Autumn is a time of ____ for home gardeners.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bradley Hall provides backyard access to the lakeshore path, and tennis courts are ____ to the building for your recreational enjoyment.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There are ____ 100 days until your final examination. It's time you started working.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A Parisian mob broke into the palace killing many of the guards, while searching for the ____ family.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This page contains a sample outline to be used as a ____ for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to ____ from the College.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She was in ____ with her parents at home and this was having a negative effect on her schoolwork.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We must ____ the scientists and experts to make the right decisions to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some doctors have suggested that their training should be less theoretical and of more ____ use.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government had to ____ from its starting position in the face of massive criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school does a lot to ____ new families, with information meetings, translation services, etc.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Curiously ____ from the report is any mention of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The immigrants probably did not ____ more than ten per cent of the population.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a standard of living ____ for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Ask the candidate to ____ what they believe to have been their most significant challenges and accomplishments in their current job or a previous job.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A ____ for other cultures is inherent in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ you to spend part of the summer vacation reading. This is an excellent way to improve your English.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the sole reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain ____ of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They faced problems for which they did not have the ____ or the training.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ when the angry parent said that he would contact his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main ____ to such Research & Development programs is the fact that the market size and the prices of the new products are unknown.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We know it's not 100% correct, but it's the best ____ that we can produce at this time.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to ____ and investigate the extent of the problem.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You have received this e-mail in the ____ belief that its contents would be of interest to you.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting ____ to raise water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ for other cultures is inherent in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of the arteries is to transport oxygen around the body.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Fish farming is an ____ that should go some way to compensating for the reduction of fish in the oceans.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ was unclear. It had been hand-drawn and then copied using weak ink.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not enough to ____ children not to play with fireworks. It should be illegal for children to buy them.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental ____ are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What would you ____ to do today? Write a dictation or watch a video?", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's a total ____ that young girls are being pressured into near-starving themselves into being too thin.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "tool", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The top ____ of this car is 230kph.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will notice an ____ that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated ____ program.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Visit our web page Phases of the Moon for a more detailed explanation and a clear ____ that shows the phases of our moon.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We are heading for a ____ in our health system. Not enough people want to be doctors.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How people react to music is subjective. What ____s good to one person may ____ terrible to another.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was no limit, it seemed, to what the terrorists who ____ America were prepared to do.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Administrators and supervisors are expected to see that those who report to them are informed about, understand and ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The tale ends with Gilgamesh, at the end of his ____ standing before the gates of Uruk.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A large ____ of the country is under water after the heavy rainfall of the last 2 weeks.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Before this century there was little ____ between them; indeed, they did not think of themselves as two distinct kinds of people.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Can you please explain the ____ by which students are placed in ESL class?", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They are currently involved in a battle ____ Occidental Petroleum to save their land and their way of life.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The research addresses teacher attitudes toward the ____ of homework.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With winter weather comes the need to prepare your home, automobile and family to ____ with the colder temperatures.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Law School will not ____ you to take a course pass/fail unless you have received written permission.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "permit", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Our very privilege makes us ____ of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Who was the first person to ____ America? Most people say it was Columbus.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Through much of the War, the U.S. and its Allies could not ____ a fully effective blockade against Germany.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The first ____ change in the business model came with Henry Ford's move toward standardization and applying the concepts of a production line to the car.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our ____ problem is how to convince the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the attempt was an ____ failure.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, despite the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When the moisture con____s, heat is released into the air, making it warmer and less ____ than its surroundings.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most people who use a wheelchair or mobility devices do not ____ them as confining. They are viewed as liberating; a means of getting around.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult ____ deserve a reward.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was a lack of consistency in programs at conferences to ____ the adviser's professional skills.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Due to the money shortage in schools, teachers are now being charged a high ____ for training.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Smartboard is an excellent ____ for teaching language.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If faculty suspect that a ____ health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police chief gave a very different version of the ____ than the TV reporter the previous day.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an ____ issue, but an internal one: the government failed to fulfill its duties.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These questions are meant to help you research the ____ information you will need to evaluate some of the water quality issues in NYC.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the importance of the internet.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the ____ of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The tour bus will ____ from Eisenstadt to travel over the border to Hungary to visit the summer palace built by Prince Nicolaus.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this report you must write a ____ of FIS and your previous school.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "statistic", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical number"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any ____ of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Professor Cowen has a particular interest in professional ____ firms and has conducted much of her research in the investment banking industry.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a ____ standard for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police have decided not to ____ the identity of the men arrested for planting the bombs.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Good teachers must engage their students as they find them, as they ____ themselves, walking in the door.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Iraq has entered into a critical ____ where there is a great danger of civil war.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When reporting scores, both the student's ____ and the number of students in the class must be stated.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always permit giving undivided ____ to the organization.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance rank is ____ of maternal rank, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest rank between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Dartmouth has received a number of complaints, specifically ____ their poor fact-checking.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we are to contemplate actions designed to ____ the pattern of current difficulties in Viet Nam we ought to lay the groundwork.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very confident that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at ____ to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What is absent in your essay is any reference to the ____ of your ideas.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has decided to block financial ____ to the African country until the civil war is over.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The internet is a ____ resource for today's students.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging task for the employers to determine the factors that ____ job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Biological processes ____ strongly with physical and chemical processes to create the planetary environment.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has only had ____ success in reducing the number of unemployed people.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I'm not sure that his parents realize the ____ of the problems he is having in school.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company was unable to ____ its recent good trade figures.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Strict laws in Germany ____ the opening of shops on a Sunday.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an external shell ____ than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The following information has been prepared to serve as a ____ to assist you in establishing criteria for a successful teaching practice.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government should not ____ young unmarried mothers by giving them free housing.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Roman walls of Oberursel still ____ and surround almost all of the old town center.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government does not ____ its citizens an explanation for every decision it makes.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Racism and prejudice continue to be a ____ problem in our country.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The project itself may grow out of course work, but it must comprise achievement that is over and above ____ course activities.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The student's answer may not ____ all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or superficial analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The organizations that take ____ for putting ecology first have failed to reform or develop a system that will allow them to achieve their goals.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Rubin did not suffer ____ but learned to use anger and pride to fight for what was right.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These documents have an ____ stamp, but I'm not convinced they are authentic.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The organizations that take ____ for putting ecology first have failed to reform or develop a system that will allow them to achieve their goals.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Let's ____ the idea that you can actually teach critical thinking skills to primary school children.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students worked in groups to ____ (or dis____) a series of mathematical statements.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The correct ____ of this text requires recovering certain implicit information that relies on commonsense knowledge.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students gain professional experience before graduation so that they ____ the job market with a distinct advantage.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will receive an email from the Financial ____ office when your financial aid eligibility has been determined.", "Opt_1": "Tradition", "Opt_2": "Aid", "Opt_3": "Decade", "Opt_4": "Series", "Answer": "Aid", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the departure times are not convenient for you, there is a list of recommended car and taxi services ____ as well.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The western end of the trade ____ appears to have developed earlier than the eastern end, principally because of the development of the empires in the west.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ is not a sufficient reward for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "London is becoming more and more unpleasant. The government needs to drastically ____ the penalty for dropping litter.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your good grades in the report ____ my expectations. Well done!", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sitting too long in front of a computer may ____ headaches or back problems.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a ____ sheet, write a thorough statement describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I cannot ____ you to listen, but I will ask you to leave the room if you talk while I do.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She should be able to ____ to take care of the children on \ufffd\ufffd200.00 per month.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you ____ the globe by 360\ufffdX, you will return to your starting point.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a committee to ____ the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher had to ____ the boy from the rest of the class. His bad behaviour was disrupting their learning.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The western end of the trade ____ appears to have developed earlier than the eastern end, principally because of the development of the empires in the west.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company does a minor ____ of business in the USA; the majority of its trade is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He is learning that treatments that worked fine in cities don't always ____ well here, where patients may drive several hours to obtain medical care.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Can you please give me an ____ of what happened while I was out of the classroom?", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an episode of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common ____ than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the school behind the car park is for seniors only.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Rubin did not ____ defeat but learned to use anger and pride to fight for what was right.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "exploit", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The price of stamps will increase only if the total volume of mail does not decrease and the postal ____ does not become more efficient.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school will ____ use of the library for all students unless the student who damaged the photocopier is found.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the ____ of competitive sports, and perhaps elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "FAQ > How do I ____ for free health services?", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Military historians and other students of international security, gradually got into the ____ of meeting together to discuss ideas.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company's efforts to ____ business over the past year failed to impress the shareholders.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is well-known that knowledge of formal grammar rules does always not ____ with the ability to teach the language.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a general rule, all persons wishing to ____ the conference must register and pay for participation.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "All this progress was a consequence of the ____ of technology and also of ____s in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The administrative staff will ____ the student supervisor when a student has failed to provide required documents and other ____ation.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This we know: the earth does not ____ to man, man ____s to the earth.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are advised to ____ serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If faculty suspect that a ____ health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This page contains a sample ____ to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong ____.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A student should ____ a Literature minor by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we accept your request to amend the information, we will make ____ efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ method of learning vocabulary is to write words and their translations in a small notebook.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To separate white light into its component colors with a prism and use an ____ prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He said the ____ now should exclude events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to achieve the results.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Having access to the laptop does seem to have substantially increased the ____ feeling of having adequate resources to do the job.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the exact word to ____ an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I find it quite hard to understand why anyone would attempt to ____ or ignore these accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We did not ____ our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or field of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A large ____ map shows a small area with a large amount of detail.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While its lack of clarity was seen by some early critics as a clear ____ of error and confusion, it was seen by others as a hallmark of genius.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is set to ____ the parents' request to extend their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Begin your paper with a brief ____ of the storyline, or a brief episode from it, that suggests or illustrates your thesis.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a minor consideration in the ____ decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government had to ____ from its starting position in the face of massive criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The goal of this unit is to teach students how a seemingly unimportant event can have a ____ effect on their lives.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It seems natural that we would want to employ nurses from overseas; after all we ____ everything else.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "omit", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave something out or not do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I ____ that difficulties at home underlie her recent poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to ____ the vast mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police have decided not to ____ the identity of the men arrested for planting the bombs.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Vehicles that do not ____ a valid parking permit will be towed immediately.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There are ____ reasons for his academic success. The most important one is his willingness to work very hard.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A thought- provoking ____ suggests we should expect the extinction of intelligent life on Earth soon.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to ____ the dispute by the efforts of the local community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The meeting will ____ at 8.30.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is too soon to ____ the success of the \"war on terror\".", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was agriculture that allowed civilizations to ____ growth.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad attitude is put on a ____. If the ____ is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university follows a strict ____ of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies ____ multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The results on the tests are ____ to expectations.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The spaceship has been sending back ____ images of Jupiter as it flies past on its way to the edge of the solar system.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a highly ____ view of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's plan to kill all infected cows in the region is sure to produce an angry ____ from the farmers.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We should avoid the ____ of assuming that we will ever be able to comprehend the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its tax proposals. They are less than clear to most people.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The United States is a nation pulling apart to a ____ unknown in the last 25 years.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In issues of accuracy or speed, the former must always have ____ over the latter.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students who seriously ____ network security or otherwise misuse the computing facilities will have their accounts terminated.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Under these treaties, US warships did not have to ____ the nature of the weapons they carried.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have learned this lesson that water and other liquids ____ sound better than air.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "\"Recommended Changes to Student Handbook\" was the next ____ for discussion.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the ____ and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people suspect that the US government knew in ____ about the terrorist attack on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The union was not able to ____ all of its goals in this budget session.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government does not plan to ____ any more immigrants unless they can prove that their life is in danger in their own country.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What is the exact change in ____ of the water when it freezes as ice?", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The report was designed to measure computer and Internet use ____ people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Would you help me with my science homework? - OK, but I'd ____ go out and play basketball.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was ____ poorly designed and therefore not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We will deviate from this ____ throughout the semester, but the hand-out gives a good impression of our general focus.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her ____ absence from school is the principal reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Later in 1975, the APA announced that homosexuality was not a ____ disorder and in 1994 they acknowledged that it was neither a ____ illness nor a moral deficiency.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the departure times are not ____ for you, there is a list of recommended car and taxi services available as well.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He both provided a message service and the ____ needed to send and receive wireless messages.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The future energy system will need to eliminate the unacceptable risk that the ____ system places on the environment.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of teachers at this school are native speakers of English.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Children are able to ____ between reality and fantasy between the ages of 3 and 5, according to new research.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some doctors have suggested that their training should be less theoretical and of more ____ use.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She was unable to justify her poor behaviour, but promised never to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to collaborate ____ our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This emphasis on improving student outcomes will persist in the immediate future as the dominant ____ in determining the success or failure of education reform strategies.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Shortage of research space remains a significant ____ for future development.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot comply with this law ____ to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To ____ for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a generation efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Assad did not want to ____ a cease-fire until Israel evacuated at least those parts of the Golan Heights occupied in the October war.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Because of their behavior in protecting food sources, it is ____ unusual to see two hummingbirds spending time together.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It must be obvious what the primary theme of each ____ is, and how that theme connects with the paper's overall theme.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The explanation for this extraordinary decision lies in the immediate ____ surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The xenon atoms need to accelerate to a ____ of 30 km/s.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is certain to ____ opposition to its proposal.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Depression can ____ from sense of tiredness, low motivation and concentration, to severe difficulties with managing one's daily life.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This requires thought, but not at a ____ which should be inaccessible to advanced students.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A series of accidents and a mounting public ____ resulted in the government licensing of pilots and aircraft.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Program is designed to ____ researchers whose ISBM-supported work appears in the academic literature.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My parents will ____ that I did this work without help.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The administration's proposal to extend the school day came under ____ from the teachers.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The price of stamps will increase only if the total volume of mail does not decrease and the postal ____ does not become more efficient.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Educational websites have the ____ suffix: .edu. For example, the URL of this website is: esl.fis.edu.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Cats and young children are similar: they both like to ____ new places.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In all such cases, we are happy to refund the ____ price and shipping charges once the prints are returned to us, at your expense, in good condition.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ example of ambiguity is the sentence: \"I do not like visiting aunts.\"", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or purpose and then hoping to ____ it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "tough", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The chairman needs to ____ a better meeting next time. The last one was very disorganized.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school offers basketball ____ in the vacation.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She was able to ____ the Smartboard screen controls so that the presentation was visible to everyone.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many people like to change the ____ on their computer desktop.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It seems that the mind cannot ____ the necessary information from what is supplied to it.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Bright flashing lights ____ headaches in some people.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These results indicate that substantial numbers of students attending the school are not attaining ____ levels of literacy and mathematical competency.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Despite the political, economic and cultural success of the Arab city states, Islam for many years did not spread into the ____ of East.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government plans to raise the money they ____ to poor countries in the Third World.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to do a better job when you ____ your work. There are far too many unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a committee to ____ the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ is not a sufficient reward for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The combination of natural and human systems adds an additional ____ of complexity to the interactions.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The administration is planning to ____ the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The results from this experimental course illustrate very clearly that flow visualization can be performed successfully by a wide ____ of people.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the long run, democratic market capitalism has proved ____ to deterministic, command socialism.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "superior", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The scientists advising EPA said they believe there is a ____ chance that the corn is an allergen.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an ____ war, trying to conceal the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from power cycle failure, but this is not a ____ for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to ____ the amount of land available for pasture.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She wanted to expand and to reorganize the departmental program but was not able to ____ the school administration.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This unnecessary ____ would adversely impact the existing review system that ensures the high quality of scientific research in the United States.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "China is, indeed, going through a ____, but it is not a ____ from capitalism to communism.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Did everyone ____ their report card.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously ____ your overall grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will represent a major challenge for ____ in general.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The current timing left the ____ with only one working week to review the applications.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They have made a fundamental ____ in the way they are thinking about the opportunities and problems their business face.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My biggest ____ about the book is that Gruchy did not insert his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore attempt to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Madrid ____ was like the September 11 ____ in that government agencies failed to share information about a potential terrorist threat.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some historians still ____ to label the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "labour", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "work", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The time has come, however, to quit spending time and money supporting ____ technologies and to concentrate on delivering better service.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They simply decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that ____ (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The University of California library system faces a ____ in relation to the costs of online journal subscriptions.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Groups should advise the instructor if a ____ is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has announced ____ plans to reduce long-term unemployment.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This ____ is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity explore topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the ____ use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some doctors have the ____ to use language that their patients do not understand.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, ____ a huge debt to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The volume of business between Europe and Asia has ____ increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I understand her ____ to speak English in class. She has only just arrived at the school.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was a visual thinker and an artist, albeit a ____ unsuccessful one.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ the plan after a meeting with the parents.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Such activity cannot be considered an adequate ____ for excellence in teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant ____ of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also ____ to accelerate environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She has ____ problems with her spelling, but the content of her writing is actually very good.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this ____ by 40%.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The report was designed to ____ computer and Internet use among people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is a ____ privilege to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He both provided a message service and the ____ needed to send and receive wireless messages.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Well done. The ____ of all your labour is an fine grade in your ESL test.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students, staff and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the public should be allowed to ____ classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Gladwin County decided to suspend the sale of dogs from its animal shelter in order to give citizens the chance to ____ the county's earlier decision.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most people are aware of the problem of ____ warming, but not many are willing to change the way they live.", "Opt_1": "independent", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The business will not ____ unless it can win new customers in foreign countries.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A very ____ response in real time is needed to record the optical emission while the gamma-ray burst is in progress.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people think that the government ____ to reduce teenage pregnancy will not be successful.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government will never win the ____ against drug-taking.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is overspending and will soon ____ all the money set aside for books and other materials.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Homes were built and sold to families in need at no ____ and no interest.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to ____ the world's languages into one comprehensive genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not precise enough to ____ exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an ____ security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In a world of infinite problems but finite resources, competition for adequate ____ and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Without a filter on perceptual input, our brains would have the impossible task of sifting through an overload of information to ____ important from unimportant information.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people like to change the ____ on their computer desktop.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to reject an ____ of the local food.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We designed an ____ to acquire blood from embryonic rats.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most beginning ESL students need a lot of ____ from their teachers and parents before they can start to work more independently.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has changed its ____ to nuclear power now that the cost of oil has been so high for the past few years.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He has only ____ control of basic verb grammar. He quite often chooses the wrong tense or forgets the -s ending.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While I don't present this as absolutely the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized ____ be adopted.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In my school ____ it is emphasized that teachers must differentiate instruction for students.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you have the amnio test late in pregnancy and are carrying a baby with Downs Syndrome, it will be too late to ____ the pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Can you ____ these dollars to Yen for me?", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dr. Glick is an ____ in community and public health nursing programs and issues.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material ____ of Louisiana, it did not diminish the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is usually easy for teachers to ____ if an ESL student has copied text from a webpage.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If the individual knows in advance when he or she wishes to apply for time away from the workplace, the individual should complete the ____ request form.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers ____ to improve student scores in standardized tests by doing 5 minutes practice at the start of every lesson.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Leadership is not a ____ that many people have.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My biggest ____ about the book is that Gruchy did not insert his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Before economists implement ____ measures to reduce population growth, further studies should be performed.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The meeting ended very late but the administration still did not have time to ____ all the issues it wanted to.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The banking ____ of Frankfurt is right in the city centre.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This document will explain some of the problems that could exist because the computer is unable to ____ updates for Windows Vista.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When we ask people to describe their characters when they are at their best, they ____ confident, hopeful, humorous, optimistic, resourceful.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The only goal of some people is to ____ as much money as possible.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government decided to ____ its economic policy after three years of very slow growth.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "alter", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was given to the grandmother by her grandfather in 1852, when the latter was a ____ of the California assembly.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The dropout ____ for high schoolers rose to 3.8 percent during the last decade.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The student was suffering from ____ and physical problems as a result of taking drugs for several months.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Drug abusers also show prefrontal cortex ____ities; it is possible that ____ behaviour may be linked to drug use.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is my firm intention to ____ with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Patients are ____ to forget information that is not written down.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some students see no motive for learning German - ____ if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All political parties have websites these days to ____ people of their policies.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this report you must write a ____ of FIS and your previous school.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I can survive on a ____ income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school will always ____ its policy of expelling students for repeated plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "ESL teachers often ask their students to ____ words in class.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most ____ problems were inappropriate vocabulary, comprising 40%. of the total errors.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Social network analysts use two kinds of tools from mathematics to ____ information about patterns of ties among social actors.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The student was suffering from mental and physical problems as a ____ of taking drugs for several months.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Infinity is an ____ idea that many students find difficult to understand.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a consequence, it often takes many years of ____ water quality data collection to statistically detect a trend.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A significant ____ of the continent is characterized by water scarcity.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a serious ____ on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is somewhat unusual considering the 1997 survey's ____ of 41%.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He came up with a ____ excuse for not doing his homework, but his teacher did not believe him.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is my firm ____ to remain with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I ____ you to prepare more carefully for tests.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased ____ in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical ____ of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "People with ____ disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to advocate for them.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is very ____ for a student to learn English so quickly. But she has!", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "logical", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "rare", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "making sense", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To ____ these opportunities, information systems will need to sense and act as well as compute.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at ____ expense to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In history lessons we learn about many ____ peoples such as the Egyptians who built the pyramids, and Roman emperors like Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The service ____ of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing ____.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "'At once' is ____ the wrong phrase; administrators soon learn that change happens gradually, that", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ will move to a 42-volt electrical system within this decade.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If a student is not in attendance during the last ____ of a semester, the instructor may report a grade of zero.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government plans to raise the money they donate to ____ countries in the Third World.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will encounter many difficulties but if you ____ in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Tests are valid when they ____ what they claim to ____, and reliable when they ____ consistently.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The outcome of our ____ is that most students are against school uniform.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you ____ to present proper identification you will be billed \ufffd\ufffd5.00 per test.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "fail", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government refused to ____ from its plan to ban smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Study suggests macroscopic bilaterian animals did not ____ until 555 million years ago.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our teachers ____ the school's philosophy that only excellence is good enough.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to ____ on your admissions application that you will have 24 credits completed at the time of attendance.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many universities make their materials ____ to students online.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the precaution to take if you decide to use email as an official ____ of communication.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "How can educators design ____ to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The practice test materials will become available just ____ to the class.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The doctor began to ____ that her patient was not telling the whole truth about what was wrong.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school charges a ____ for outside clubs to use its sports facilities.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A battle to save life has ____ been waged at the Kwangtze Hospital in Shanghai. This battle is not yet over, but it has already caused a great sensation.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your response was unclear. Could you please ____ it.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The substantial advantages of these close personal relationships far ____ the disadvantages of remaining small.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The main ____ to such Research & Development programs is the fact that the market size and the prices of the new products are unknown.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He has made substantial ____ this trimester.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ Einstein to your list of famous scientists.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Would you help me with my science homework? - OK, but I'd ____ go out and play basketball.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Could you please ____ the homework for me? I'm not sure I understand.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this section of the survey, having an ____ privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We further believe that the general quality of student writing will not improve unless we as a department are willing to ____ explicitly the standards we require.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If they want to ____ more business, they will have to reduce their prices.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For the first time in history, the federal government will ____ college and university admissions.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "confront", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to remove greenhouse gases from the ____ without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The World Bank plans to ____ 50% more money to developing countries in the new year.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The purpose of this study is to investigate the ____ that men are better in mathematics than women.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While I am not in favor of teaching creationism in public schools, I am also not ____ to having it presented and examined.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are approximately 350 students in high school. I'm not sure of the ____ number.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Can you please give me the ____ version of your writing? This looks like your first draft before you corrected the spelling and grammar.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Despite the overall satisfaction that the program was ____ successful, there are several ways in which the program could have been improved.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The computer lab is ____ to the library.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most language teachers use ____ aids in the classroom, such as pictures or objects.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you want your letter to be a private communication, I usually do not ____ sending copies to other people, since they may decide to act on the matter.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion ____ the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My ____ is that she has started working too late to pass her examinations.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If UVA is to increase ____ of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Assign students to groups; ____ rules for participation, and rotate jobs within each group.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "C. S. Lewis tackled this ____ head-on and offered some good advice that informs how we select our projects.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The libraries are in a poor ____ and are in urgent need of restocking with new books and journals in both Arabic and English.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Manufacturing companies are finding it difficult to make a profit, because of the ____ in the price of oil.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Musical ____ is a trait that some people are born with, but no-one succeeds as a musician without an enormous amount of practice.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "\"We hope to preserve the historic value of these buildings and ____ serious parties to step", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Board may ____ that those actions created a hostile or abusive work environment which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is confident that the summer ____ cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In some countries anyone caught taking drugs can expect a very ____ punishment.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The district cannot ____ the accuracy of the information or the appropriateness of any material that a student finds.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most older cultures seem to accept volcanoes as a natural part of life and ____ their habits accordingly.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How can educators design ____ to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages ____ from a moderate amount of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "benefit", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Previous experience in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an ____ but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The US government plan to develop weapons that can be used from space. Many scientists, however, ____ the proposals as unworkable.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The university plans to establish a ____ so that poorer students can attend.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The good results in recent matches ____ that the new trainer knows what he is doing.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will need to form project teams of two or three students, and then it will be your responsibility to ____ meetings.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Web sites such as Wikipedia certainly ____ the finding of information, although not all of it is reliable.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most of the families at our international school are here for a ____ of 2-3 years The ____ of the Earth's orbit around the sun is 365 days.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ for other cultures is inherent in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Education Department's increased demand for paperwork will ____ the patience and good will of teachers.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many talented ____ young people have had to forego graduate or professional education because of lack of access to such programs.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The doctor's claim was ____ hypocrisy. He more interested in making money than his patient's health.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Turkish law requires foreign scholars to obtain ____ permission to carry out research at institutions in Turkey.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ of nature is the way a stick seems to break when it is looked at under water.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nevertheless, thirty-three years later, Israel is not willing to ____ from the Golan Heights to the 4 June 1967, prewar border.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please do not ____ me. I know what I said is correct.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not ____ the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a positive racial identity.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "appreciate", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "reserve", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to publish if the ____ of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The search results are likely to include lots of hits that are not particularly ____ to your topic.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "artificial", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The students decided to ____ in their attempt to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We should never praise or ____ any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ was first observed in 1911 by Onnes, who noted that the resistance of a frozen mercury rod abruptly dropped to zero.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Each section of the book, is represented by a family, which was chosen as an ____ family representing that country.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The volume of business between Europe and Asia has ____ increased in recent years.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The twins ____ most of the weekend to their fishing hobby.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ was that starving the brain of sugar would kill marginally functioning brain cells, but the therapy was soon phased out because it was considered too dangerous.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an ____ meeting in order to share what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "My teacher has the ____ of telling us the homework in the last minute of the lesson. It's not good.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to ____ the cost of complying with new requirements regarding data recording.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to develop methods to ____ a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Previous experience in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an ____ but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher was asked to ____ after it was discovered that he had lied about his absence from school.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are interested in checking out any of the books in the ____ case, please inquire at Circulation.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We need to ____ a test to measure the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lord Wavell had to ____ as he could not bring about a settlement and he was succeeded by Lord Mountbatten.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For most children, two parents are better than one for more than just ____ reasons.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We reserve the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide ____ identification.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Engineers were deeply concerned about the O-ring ____ on the booster rocket before the launch, but were unable to convince managers at NASA of the importance of that problem.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government was fully aware of the ____ of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If the demonstrations continue much longer, they will ____ the government to change its plans.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While the Spartans were principally responsible for the victory, the Athenian fleet was probably the most important ____ of that victory.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is fair to praise the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment ____ older people.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For some people the ____ of a car is more important than its price or performance.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This note describes a scoring scheme for the co-reference ____ in MUC6.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The reduction in personal tax is intended to ____ spending because people will have more money in their pockets.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These instruction and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are ____ (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The goal of this unit is to teach students how a seemingly unimportant event can have a significant ____ on their lives.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "occur", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school is set to ____ the parents' request to extend their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The document was intended to ____ everything from minerals, through the kingdom of plants, to the highest animals.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a revolution in electrical energy leading to the construction of ____ stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school has set up a ____ so that less wealthy students can attend.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is very little ____ of the poor and middle class as our corrupt judges have developed a system called lawyer denial.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many a ____ that was once believed by everyone later proves to be false - e.g. that the sun goes around the earth.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university intend to make some changes in its admissions policy, but it cannot yet ____ what those changes will be.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His observations were not ____ enough to conclude anything significant about nocturnal behaviour.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the ____ plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, especially in the case of an ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You do not need to be an ____ in computers to make a web page or send an email.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ how the government can hope to win the forthcoming election.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Children visiting the internet chatrooms are advised not to ____ their real names.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is during adolescence that clear gender differences ____ which might contribute to the varying rates of depression.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to impose a ____ on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Asian companies are good at building small cars but will never ____ the mainstream US car market.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school chose not to ____ news of the teacher's accident.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If men and women do ____ jobs they should earn ____ pay.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Honesty is not an ____ that most people associate with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My ESL teacher has the ____ to talk about his own school days.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Perhaps we will have to ____ the issue of the 'Child Friendly City'.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a ____ move, but frankly we didn't have a choice.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do not ____ all your energy in the first 20 minutes. Remember that the game lasts for half an hour!", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Although we did ____ the faculty in the revised teaching methods, in hindsight our ____ing was not thorough enough to prepare them for the new course.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sometimes it becomes more important to modify tried-and-tested methods and habits rather than ____ more resources.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of ____ White jurors.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The population of the world is will ____ to increase. It is expected that there will be 7 billion people on earth in the year 2010.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The proposed system seems an improbable ____ for the short-term, given that a half century of work with this goal has met only limited success.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company was heavily in ____ after investing a lot of money in new machinery.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Excellent writing with just one or two ____ mistakes!", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The bottom of the Pacific Ocean is the most ____ region on Earth.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The referee decided ____ the game because of the predicted thunderstorm.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material ____ of Louisiana, it did not diminish the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ the cafeteria at lunchtime. It's too crowded and noisy.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Although the agreement was ____ rather than voluntary, it led to substantial military reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a ____ tax sheltered annuity program should contact their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As incoming college students have arrived, I've compiled a list of all the truly important things that you need to have to ____ this experience.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "comprise", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our chief problem is how to ____ the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The main cause of her poor grades are her ____ absences from school.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "often"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please bring all your ____ to class. That includes your homework planner and dictionary.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Congress seems to have taken a cautious approach to regulating a technology that is reinventing the very ____ in which ideas are expressed.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people suspect that the US government knew in ____ about the terrorist attack on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ for her frequent absences will be a poor grade in the final exam.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a strong ____ between what the government promised to do and what it has actually achieved.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people think that the government's proposals to reduce teenage crime are ____ and will not work.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A verbal contract is impossible to prove, and the organization will always ____ that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I often find it difficult to ____ my advice so that the ESL beginners in the class can understand me.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Ambition was not an ____ of the female characters in his earlier films.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ the stairs by the nurse's office, you will see the cafeteria in front of you.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base regarding the ____ of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the hierarchy and follow their ____ visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "analyze", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She is so ____ in German class. It's no wonder that she can hardly speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some tests may be very ____ but too costly to run, while others are less costly but not as precise.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many businesses offer ____ working hours. Employees can arrive early and leave early or arrive late and leave late.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ the dimension of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You are definitely going to fail the ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you do not ____ the rules of the classroom, you will be sent to the headmaster.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I don't believe you made a ____ effort to improve. Your grades certainly have not got better.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration refuse to modify its goals in order to ____ a consensus?", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Bradley Hall provides backyard access to the lakeshore path, and tennis courts are ____ to the building for your recreational enjoyment.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Audio software can help students to record their spoken words describing an abstract ____ or how to perform a computation.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The first ____ of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others among the body of students.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The bulk of the urban districts, particularly in the Northern states, were totally ____ to this development.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Which activity are you going to ____ next time? - I think I'll try chess.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows ____ to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to recover it.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is important to note, however, that rankings are just one of ____ tools to use in evaluating the many and varied educational programs offered.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise ____ of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In his view, the Empire was less a place where England exerted control than where it lost command of its ____ identity.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "stipulate", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to require", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government plans to raise the money they ____ to poor countries in the Third World.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This brochure was created to help home owners and land managers recognize hazardous defects in trees and to ____ possible corrective actions.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Car companies spend a considerable ____ of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I believe that the DOD (Department of Defense) should ____ this discriminatory policy.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ his strange behaviour recently is the result of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The two teams are roughly equal. It's difficult to ____ who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Historically, there was ____ for crop and livestock losses, but the problem of estimating the damage and lack of funds for ____ programs has been significant.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My ____ to work every day takes me past my old school.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The scientists advising EPA said they believe there is a ____ chance that the corn is an allergen.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is very satisfying as a teacher to see the ____ in the ability of your students.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most comprehensive ____ of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When two atoms of hydrogen ____ with one of oxygen, then the result is H2O, water.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The library is going to ____ a new electronic system for checking out books.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mr. Bush cannot answer Sheehan's question and he cannot ____ the war of aggression against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "invisible", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Rexhepi said the incident damaged the atmosphere for the upcoming talks on ____ matters between Kosovar and Serbian officials.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to the severe shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to ____ a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "University staff will ____ the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages instead of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of scarce resources ____ competing ends.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As a simple soldier he gained much ____ by conducting a retreat after all the superior officers had been killed or wounded.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some teachers believe that it is better to teach language to a class with students of ____ ability.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is a ____ chance to visit South Africa, and at the same time help build a school in the desert.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government tried hard to ____ its decision, but most people believe it was a serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a ____ over a legitimate issue.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ needs to consist of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of ____ White jurors.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government needs to overcome its ____ to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Children who have no ____ to their behaviour are often unhappy.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you want to be successful in business, it is certainly an ____ to be able to speak more than one language.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When you ____ the school, turn right and walk along the corridor. You will find the library on the left-hand side.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government looks likely to ____ in its objective to reduce child poverty by the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We should not ____ the possibility that house prices will begin to fall.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Bible laid down some rules for the humane treatment of slaves but did not ____ the practice.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Al Gore absolutely did not deserve the Nobel peace prize. On a personal level, he has not reduced his ____ carbon dioxide emissions.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Scientists are working very hard to find a ____ for oil. They hope that one day cars will not pollute the atmosphere.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The weather ____ for tomorrow says that we can expect showers and a little weak sunshine.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I find it quite hard to understand why anyone would attempt to ____ or ignore these accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree that thought disorder and language disorder are ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If someone invites you to their party, it's polite to send them a ____ and tell them if you can come or not.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I don't believe you made a ____ effort to improve. Your grades certainly have not got better.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also threaten to ____ environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In my opinion the government's ____ for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many people believe that the 'war on terror' will be a ____ war.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Web sites such as Wikipedia certainly ____ the finding of information, although not all of it is reliable.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Telephone and telegraph ____ from the Greek words meaning far speak and far write.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thus, there is no question but that the donor intends this gift to be for the ____ use of Princeton University.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Above all, a teacher must be ____ when dealing with requests for grade changes and other related matters.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Farmers rotate their crops. This means that they do not grow the same thing on the same ____ for more than one year.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has passed laws to give equal rights to minority groups, but it can do nothing to ____ the prejudice that exists inside some people's heads.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a very ____ problem. We need more time to think of a good solution.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Where did you ____ your knowledge of ocean ecology?.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "On the one ____ I got to school early, the building was closed because of a fire alarm.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has little chance of success in its ____ to reduce crime unless it creates more jobs.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "struggle", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has stated that it will not ____ its decision to ban smoking in pubs.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Are you ____ of the fact that you may fail the course?", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The boss took the ____ decision to close the factory for a week.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ is planning to extend the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "advise", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Demonstrators tried to ____ the opening of the new airport runway.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Very few companies can ____ cars of the quality of German makes such as BMW or Mercedes.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new factory near the school will ____ parts for mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The following information has been prepared to serve as a ____ to assist you in establishing criteria for a successful teaching practice.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Of ____ she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the initial stage of learning English.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This project involves students in the process of learning in an attempt to ____ their skills and their successes across all areas of the course.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The best ____ of your essay is the fact that it was very easy to follow your line of argument.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the ____ that urban life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This ____ is being used to gather information about the current level of frustration with computers and the extent to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Knowledge about hazards plays a central but curious role in ____ perception.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ the cafeteria at lunchtime. It's too crowded and noisy.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ for recording TV programmes onto a video cassette is often very complicated.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Not any of these persons shall perform or permit any practice that may ____ the reputation of the university.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "With regret, we have had to cancel the upcoming program on \"The Nervous System\" ____ to an unavoidable change in schedules.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Of course she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the ____ stage of learning English.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the student as the school's primary customer provides an important guiding principle for many of today's school reforms.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "bulk", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "notion", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a minor consideration in the purchase ____ for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "level"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My father is going to ____ to Germany at the end of 2004.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to exert ____ in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Howard has many chances to ____ into a better father and husband, but he fails to do so.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The latest ____ among the girls in the school is to wear different colour socks.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I am surprised at the directors' ____ inability to understand how the workers are feeling.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "urban", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The 9-11 Commission failed to mention or ____ the multiple war game exercises that were being conducted that day, out of the White House.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Lispeth took to Christianity readily, and did not ____ it when she reached womanhood.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The meeting ended very late but the ____ still did not have time to cover all the issues it wanted to.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ error in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The best proof of this is that the institutional unity provided for by the Treaty of Maastricht did not ____ for even one year after the treaty was ratified.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Prices have risen by ____ 4% over the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She stopped smoking and started exercising. As a ____ her health improved considerably.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The grant is not a sufficient ____ for the excellence and hard work of this faculty and staff.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not always possible to ____ a cause of a conflict from a consequence of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If faculty suspect that a ____ health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ will send the letter of recommendation directly to the institution, but we cannot release it to the student without the letter writer's permission.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The older population of the U.S. and the world is growing rapidly, and these large numbers will represent a major ____ for society in general.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The data center will ____ researchers through the application of mathematics and computer science to biological problems.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "fade", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to disappear slowly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ your ideas a little better. It's difficult to follow what you are trying to say.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The current program ____ process is not very valuable because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sufficient progress has been made with regard to drinking water to place within reach the target of halving the proportion of the population without ____ to safe drinking water between 1990 and 2015.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to prepare an ____ that will assist you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ the classroom doors to make them less easy to break down.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Fish farming is an ____ that should go some way to compensating for the reduction of fish in the oceans.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most programs have experienced the need to develop mechanisms to ____ involvement of parents and/or guardians in the juvenile drug court process.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is principally because they ____ the church and family as sources of emotional support.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to ____ in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The United Mine Workers was the recognized bargaining ____ for the coal miners in Illinois, Indiana, Ohio, and Pennsylvania.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I find it quite hard to understand why anyone would attempt to ____ or ignore these accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that credit cards are a ____ solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We need one more teacher to ____ the cafeteria at lunch times.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teacher spoke so fast that it was difficult to ____ all the information he was giving.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not ____ of the property at any price.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Water is very ____ in many parts of North Africa.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "On hearing of the terrorist ____ the president called an immediate meeting of his top advisers.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many learners of English have problems with the spelling. Furthermore, many Asian students find the articles ____ difficult to use correctly.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The main indicator of the sanitary ____ of drinking water is the coliform bacteria count.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Columbus did not ____ slavery to the New World; the practice existed there before his arrival.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The management is hoping that its new improved product will ____ increased profits.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Production of oil and gas will ____ unless new reserves of oil and gas are discovered and developed.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The quality of your work has improved ____ in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "ESL students fare better in classrooms where the teacher is ____ of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has set up a committee to ____ why more young people have started smoking in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ we are going to have a test on this. - You are right!", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "While we must oppose all terrorism, and we have many local enemies in ____ parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding certain sentences that contradict ____ sense.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You must ____ the US using the visa document issued by the institution you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Megan Wood said although students were more educated on the issues, many did not vote simply because they forgot to ____ an application form.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The quality of your work has improved ____ in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When the USA expelled two Russian diplomats, the Russian ____ was to do the same.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a challenge for astrophysicists to explain, they ____ feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "One ____ of the internet that concerns many parents and teachers is that a huge amount of very offensive material is just a click away.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The merger of two sellers of that product in the area could not ____ market power significantly.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A student who is in ____ to the University at the end of any academic term shall not be permitted to register in the University again.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}]]